<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Richard Faltings</title><link>https://rfaltings.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Richard Faltings</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rfaltings.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Research</title><link>https://rfaltings.github.io/research/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rfaltings.github.io/research/</guid><description>Working papers Rot-Jaune-Verde. Language and Favoritism: Evidence from Swiss Soccer (2022) with Alex Krumer and Michael Lechner. Forthcoming, Kyklos
Squeezing More Juice Out of Lime: Optimal Pricing in Shared Vehicle Platforms (2023). Draft to be uploaded soon!
Work in progress Optimal Contract Commitment Structures: Evidence from Trucking.
Equilibria in Decentralized Freight Networks with Nick Buchholz and John Lazarev.
A reinforcement learning approach to dynamic pricing.</description></item><item><title>Other</title><link>https://rfaltings.github.io/other/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rfaltings.github.io/other/</guid><description>Honors I am a 2021 Twitch Research fellow
I am also a beneficiary of the UT Austin Continuing Fellowship for the 2021-2022 Academic Year.
Code I created a package to generate simple normal form games and sample solutions for students.
See the code here and a live demonstration here.
Website This website is built using Hugo with a theme forked from Archie. The email unscrambling JavaScript is from Jeff Donahue.</description></item><item><title>Introduction to Reinforcement Learning for Economists</title><link>https://rfaltings.github.io/posts/rl_econ/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rfaltings.github.io/posts/rl_econ/</guid><description>Run on Google Colab to test out the code!
The purpose of this post is to introduce some basic concepts from the reinforcement learning (RL) literature using the setting and notation that is familiar to economists studying infinite horizon dynamic decision problems. In particular, I make use of Rust (1987)'s bus engine replacement problem as a demonstrative example.
Note: the methods discussed here are mainly concerned with solving the dynamic problem, and not with estimation.</description></item></channel></rss>